# PATRICK LYNCH

Dublin • 0861970969 • plyn99@gmail.com

#### Sales Assistant

C11	m	m	1	nτ	7
Su	ш	ш	a	ΙŊ	/

Many years working in retail Solid background in providing outstanding service and building customer relationships. Strong team ethic and committed to excellence. I am Self-motivated, punctual and reliable.

I have keen Interests In web design. My educational background Is in Business Management and Computer Applications but I am self-taught in many programs such as HTML, CSS.

# Work experience

#### October 2001 - Present Sales assistant

#### Tesco Ireland

- Deliver excellent customer service.
- Assisting as part of a team.
- Organize store, allowing items to be easily located and ensuring the store is aesthetically appealing.
- Answered phone calls and cashiered the front register and stocked and shrink-wrapped pallets and shelves.
- Assisted customers with locating their purchases and placed special orders.
- Ensured store cleanliness, deliveries and built up displays and end caps.

## 2016 - Present

# Administrative assistant

#### Pat Lynch Transport Ltd

This role involves administration work including preparation of invoices, payment collection, assisting with customer queries via email & over the phone. I have assisted in on-site jobs, manual handling, heavy lifting & removals. In this position, I have developed my communication, organization & customer service skills.

### Education

1998 - 2003 Leaving Certificate

O'Connells CBS

01/09/2003 -FEATC level 5, ICM, Diploma In Business Management and Computer Applications 01/06/2005

Colaiste Dhulaigh Collage of Further Education

eBusiness Studies; Information Technology; Computer Applications; The Internet; International Business Communications; Marketing; Organisational Behaviour; Accounting; Numeracy & Statistics; Business Management & Administration; Business Law; Economics;



# Certifications

- ECDL 2016, 7 Modules Certified
- WSC, CSS Basics Certification
- WSC, HTML & CSS Fundamentals Certification
- Free Code Camp, Responsive Web Design Certification